{
    "quizTitle": "Css Crusaders ",
    "quizSynopsis": "How familiar are you with CSS? Select the correct answer to these ten common technical interview questions and see where you stand.",
    "questions": [
      {
        "answers": [
          "Static",
          "Relative",
          "Inherit ",
          "Fixed "
        ],
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a CSS position state?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "correctAnswer": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which three ways can CSS styles be applied to a web page?",
        "answers": [
          "Inline, Internal, and External",
          "Inline, JS, and Combined",
          "Inline, Tagged, and External",
          "Inline, Internal, and Web"
        ],
        "questionType": "text",
        "correctAnswer": "1"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "Margin",
          "Border",
          "Content",
          "Width"
        ],
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT part of the CSS box model?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "correctAnswer": "4"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "Selector and Declaration ",
          "Tag and Declaration ",
          "Selector and Definition ",
          "Class and Declaration "
        ],
        "question": "What are the two parts of a Ruleset? ",
        "correctAnswer": "1",
        "questionType": "text"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "With two colons (ex: a::hover)",
          "With one colon (ex: a:hover)",
          "With one semi-colon (ex: a;hover)",
          "With a period (ex: a.hover)"
        ],
        "question": "What is the correct way to define a pseudo class?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "correctAnswer": "1"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "Bulma ",
          "Bootstrap",
          "Semantic UI",
          "Style UI"
        ],
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a CSS framework?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "correctAnswer": "4"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "#",
          "@",
          "*",
          ";"
        ],
        "question": "Which selector will apply style to all elements on a web page?",
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "questionType": "text"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "With one colon (ex: p:first-line)",
          "With two colons (ex: p::first-line)",
          "With a semi-colon (ex: p;first-line)",
          "With a period (ex: p.first-line)"
        ],
        "question": "What is the correct way to define a pseudo element?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "correctAnswer": "2"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "Rational and Radical ",
          "Blended and Radical",
          "Linear and Static",
          "Linear and Radical"
        ],
        "question": "What are the two types of gradients in CSS?",
        "correctAnswer": "4",
        "questionType": "text"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "px",
          "em",
          "hz",
          "vh"
        ],
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a measurement unit in CSS?",
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "questionType": "text"
      }
    ]
  }